[
    {
        "Question": "scattered",
        "Answer": "widely separated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "option",
        "Answer": "choice",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "upper-class",
        "Answer": "noble",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "context",
        "Answer": "environment",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "progressive",
        "Answer": "increasing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "verify",
        "Answer": "establish the truth of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "endangered",
        "Answer": "not abundant",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "drawbacks",
        "Answer": "disadvantages",
        "Options": "problem"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dwelling",
        "Answer": "living",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "shifts",
        "Answer": "changes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "unique among",
        "Answer": "different from all other",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abandoned",
        "Answer": "no longer occupied",
        "Options": "left alone/ give up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "artificial",
        "Answer": "human-made",
        "Options": "not real"
    },
    {
        "Question": "enrich",
        "Answer": "enhance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "avenue",
        "Answer": "means",
        "Options": "methods"
    },
    {
        "Question": "friction",
        "Answer": "conflict",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concise",
        "Answer": "simple",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disband",
        "Answer": "dismiss",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "resolve",
        "Answer": "find a solution for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "trapped",
        "Answer": "caught",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "create",
        "Answer": "invent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "analogous to",
        "Answer": "similar",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "conserve",
        "Answer": "save",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "severity",
        "Answer": "harshness",
        "Options": "seriousness"
    },
    {
        "Question": "erroneous",
        "Answer": "wrong",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "burgeon",
        "Answer": "expand",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "collective",
        "Answer": "group",
        "Options": "gather"
    },
    {
        "Question": "postulated",
        "Answer": "hypothesized",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "expanded",
        "Answer": "was enlarged",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "faded from",
        "Answer": "disappeared from",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deliberations",
        "Answer": "discussions",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consequence",
        "Answer": "importance",
        "Options": "result"
    },
    {
        "Question": "bias",
        "Answer": "prejudice",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "comparative",
        "Answer": "relative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "predominate",
        "Answer": "are in the majority",
        "Options": "principal/ mainly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "severe",
        "Answer": "extreme",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "kept pace with",
        "Answer": "matched the increase in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dense",
        "Answer": "thick",
        "Options": "more crowded"
    },
    {
        "Question": "perpetuated",
        "Answer": "continued",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "core",
        "Answer": "center",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "crisis",
        "Answer": "critical situation",
        "Options": "disturbance"
    },
    {
        "Question": "includes",
        "Answer": "contains",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exercised",
        "Answer": "applied",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "erratic",
        "Answer": "unpredictable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outdated",
        "Answer": "old-fashioned",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "evade",
        "Answer": "escape",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "commence",
        "Answer": "begin",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "capacity",
        "Answer": "available storage space",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "annual",
        "Answer": "yearly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "formulated",
        "Answer": "developed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "principally",
        "Answer": "mainly",
        "Options": "major"
    },
    {
        "Question": "portable",
        "Answer": "moveable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hitherto",
        "Answer": "at first",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dicimate",
        "Answer": "destroy",
        "Options": "destruct"
    },
    {
        "Question": "margins",
        "Answer": "edges",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mutually exclusive",
        "Answer": "if one of the theories is true, then all the others must be false",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indefinitely",
        "Answer": "without limit",
        "Options": "endlessly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prestigious",
        "Answer": "highly regarded",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "unrivaled",
        "Answer": "unequaled",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "close",
        "Answer": "careful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dim",
        "Answer": "decrease",
        "Options": "weak"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dangle",
        "Answer": "hang",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "afford",
        "Answer": "offer",
        "Options": "provide"
    },
    {
        "Question": "intercourse",
        "Answer": "exchange",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pondered",
        "Answer": "thought about",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "delight",
        "Answer": "please",
        "Options": "pleasure"
    },
    {
        "Question": "splendid",
        "Answer": "magnificent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "carried on",
        "Answer": "continued",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "eventually",
        "Answer": "in the end",
        "Options": "overtime/ at a later time"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dwellers",
        "Answer": "inhabitants",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inhibit",
        "Answer": "restrict/ restrain",
        "Options": "slow down"
    },
    {
        "Question": "fused",
        "Answer": "combined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "massive",
        "Answer": "very large/ enormous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "costly",
        "Answer": "expensive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "marked",
        "Answer": "considerable",
        "Options": "noticeable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "elongate",
        "Answer": "stretch",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "harnessed",
        "Answer": "utilized",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "retarding",
        "Answer": "slowing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dynamic",
        "Answer": "active",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "evoke",
        "Answer": "arouse",
        "Options": "produce/ promote"
    },
    {
        "Question": "antithesis",
        "Answer": "opposite",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outbreak",
        "Answer": "sudden increase",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "foremost",
        "Answer": "earliest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "celebrated",
        "Answer": "famous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mechanisms",
        "Answer": "parts",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "features",
        "Answer": "aspects",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disguised",
        "Answer": "hidden",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "unaltered",
        "Answer": "unchanged",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "primordial",
        "Answer": "present at the very beginning ",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diffuse",
        "Answer": "spread",
        "Options": "disperse"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ultimately",
        "Answer": "eventually/ finally",
        "Options": "in the end"
    },
    {
        "Question": "daring",
        "Answer": "bold",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fostered",
        "Answer": "encouraged",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accidental",
        "Answer": "unintentional",
        "Options": "unexpected"
    },
    {
        "Question": "extensive",
        "Answer": "large",
        "Options": "widespread"
    },
    {
        "Question": "accessible",
        "Answer": "available/ reachable",
        "Options": "easy to obtain"
    },
    {
        "Question": "execute",
        "Answer": "perform",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concentrate",
        "Answer": "increase the density of population",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "complement",
        "Answer": "add to",
        "Options": "supplement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "demanded",
        "Answer": "required",
        "Options": "needed"
    }
]